public class hello
	public static void main (String[] args)
{
	double r = 10;
	double circ = 2*Math.PI*r;
	double area = Math.PI*Math.pow(r,2);
	System.out.println(circ);
	System.out.println(area);

}
Declaring a Variable - One way
	(class name do not contain number, 
public class xyz
{
	public static void main(String[] args)
	{
		String name;
		int number_of_fingers;
		double radius;
		radius = 20.231;
	}
}

Syntax for variable declaration (second way)
	type variable_name
	+ variable_names should start with a letter(upper or lower case)
	+ variable names should only include letters, numbers and underscores.
	+ variable names can not contain reserved words (int, string, double).

The Scanner object allows us to obtain user input.
To create a Scanner object, we need to:
	- Put the import statement at the top of the Java line.
	- Create a Scanner object, as shown in the first line of the main method:
		Scanner in = new Scanner(System.in) <nhập số từ bàn phím> <dòng lệnh khai báo cho người dùng nhập giá trị của biến>




